{"data":[{"question":"We were married for twenty-five years, Helen. You could at least give me a chance to run.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"were married","b":"twenty-five years","c":"at least","d":"chance to run","answer":"1","explain":" - Were married->have been married","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"Their room had such a very unpleasant view that it makes them feel quite miserable.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Their room","b":"such","c":"very unpleasant view","d":"it makes","answer":"4","explain":" - It makes-> makes","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"I don't know why she talks in so a loud voice.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"I don't know","b":"she talks","c":"so","d":"a loud voice","answer":"3","explain":" - So-> such","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"Because it was a long time since I knew him. I am not sure if I will remember him.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was","b":"a long time","c":"sure if","d":"remember him","answer":"1","explain":" - Was-> has been","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"American colonists used an extensive system of barter in order to a lack of money and credit might be overcome.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"American colonists","b":"extensive system","c":"in order to","d":"might be overcome","answer":"3","explain":" - In order to-> so that","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"We are going to stop here for a moment to get some petrols.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are going to stop","b":"here","c":"for a moment","d":"petrols","answer":"4","explain":" - Petrols->petrol","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"One way to save words is by using infinitive phrase instead to clauses.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"One way","b":"is","c":"using infinitive","d":"instead to","answer":"4","explain":" - Instead to-> instead of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"The main office of the factory can be found in Mapple Street in New York city.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The main","b":"be found","c":"in","d":"in","answer":"3","explain":" - In-> on","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"If a small child plays with matches, he or she might get burnt.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"If","b":"small child","c":"plays with","d":"might","answer":"4","explain":" - Might-> may","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"Is finish a job you have started very important to you?\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Is","b":"finish","c":"have started","d":"to you","answer":"4","explain":" - To you-> for you","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"}]}